okay a lot of you have found my whole
unit revieww videos helpful and you know
that makes a bald man smile but in the
comments y'all are like himler where are
the rest of those videos like for the AP
histories I've got units 1 through four
covered for gov I've got units 1 through
two and for Human Geography I've got
units 1 through 3 so where are the rest
well those videos do exist but they're
not here on YouTube those unit review
videos can only be found in my himler
review guides for those subjects and if
you're studying for your exams I highly
recommend that you check it out because
it's the fastest and most complete way
to get everything you need to get a five
on that National exam look if you can't
do that I totally understand you can
just chill with all my free stuff here
on YouTube but anyway that's the answer
that's where those videos are and I'll
catch you on the flipflop I'm L out